### CONTACTS

ragegypt@yahoo.com



(2+) 01221818098 (2+) 01011303084



Giza - El Sheikh Zaid

ragab-kh-gomaa-a6551429

### **SKILLS**

Computer skills 📥 Management skills

Communication



Leadership



Problem-

skills

solving

## **LANGUAGES**

**English** French

# **RAGAB KHAMIS GOMAA**

I Acquired A Good Grasp of Knowledge and Experience in Digital Transformation Field Through Working as A Supervisor, Trainer, and I was Involved in Many Domains Related To The Digital Transformation Current Studies, And PhD Research.

Trainer and Training Director with 18 years' experience. who helps participants obtain the knowledge and skills they need to thrive in a fast-paced setting. Develops interpersonal skills while offering a complete and thorough Training plan.

# **EXPERIENCE**

### **EXECUTIVE OFFICER**

2012 - Present

**GOVERNMENT TRAINING** MINISTRY OF COMMUNICATIONS AND INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

#### **QUALITY ASSURANCE SUPERVISOR**

2007 - 2012

INTERNATIONAL COMPUTER DRIVING LICENSE PROGRAM MINISTRY OF COMMUNICATIONS AND INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

### SUPERVISORY SPECIALIST

2005 - 2007

**TECHNOLOGY CENTER** 

MINISTRY OF STATE FOR ADMINISTRATIVE DEVELOPMENT

### **SUPERVISOR IN TRAINING**

2007 - 2009

TRAINING INDUSTRY STUDENTS PROGRAM

**NEW HORIZON COMPANY** 

### SUPERVISOR IN TRAINING

2004 - 2007

TRAINING YOUTH PROGRAM

ARAB ACADEMY FOR SCIENCE TECHNOLOGY & MARITIME TRANSPORT

# **ACADEMIC EXPERIENCE**

### **LECTURER HUMAN RESOURCES & SAS**

2023 - Present

ARAB ACADEMY FOR MANAGEMENT, BANKING AND FINANCIAL SCIENCES

### **LECTURER BUSINESS MANAGEMENT**

2020 - Present

**IGATE UNIVERSITY** 

### **LECTURER DIGITAL TRANSFORMATION**

2019 - Present

**FREELANCER** 

#### **INSTRUCTOR** 2018 - Present

CISCO ACADEMY PROGRAM

NATIONAL ACADEMY OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY FOR PERSONS WITH **DISABILITIES** 

**INSTRUCTOR** 2010 - Present

**CISCO ACADEMY PROGRAM** 

**E-LEARNING COMPETENCE CENTER (ELCC)** 

### **CURRICULUM VITAE**

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

IBDL
PMP
SAS Visual Analytics Basics
SAS Visual Analytics Advanced
Government Sector Management
TOT
Training Specialist
ICDL
IT Essentials
A+ Certified Professional
CCAI
Cybersecurity Introduction

**Cybersecurity Essentials** 

**INSTRUCTOR** 2008 - 2018

**GOVERNMENT SERVICES** 

MINISTRY OF STATE FOR ADMINISTRATIVE DEVELOPMENT

**INSTRUCTOR** 2006 - 2011

TRAINING YOUTH PROGRAM

ARAB ACADEMY FOR SCIENCE TECHNOLOGY & MARITIME TRANSPORT

# **EDUCATION**

PHILOSOPHIAE DOCTOR RESEARCHER (PhD( HUMAN RESOURCES & DIGITAL TRANSFORMATION

**DOCTORAL OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION (DBA)** 

BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION BENI-SUEF UNIVERSITY

**MASTER OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION (MBA)** 

HUMAN RESOURCES ESLSCA UNIVERSITY

**POSTGRADUATE DIPLOMA (PGDIP)** 

HUMAN RESOURCES CAIRO UNIVERSITY

**POSTGRADUATE DIPLOMA (PGDIP)** 

BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION CAIRO UNIVERSITY

**BACHELOR OF SCIENCE** 

COMMERCE SOUTH VALLEY UNIVERSITY

# **KNOWLEDGE AND COURSES**

DIGITALIZATION DIPLOMA British Council

**DIGITAL TRANSFORMATION** National Telecommunications Institute

**DIGITAL TRANSFORMATION AND FINTECH FEPS Business Incubator** 

VIRTUAL LEADERSHIP FOR THE DIGITAL AGE Attaa Digital

**DIGITAL TRANSFORMATION INITIATIVE** International Digital Transformation Club

CERTIFIED DIGITAL CITIZEN National Council for Training and Education

DIGITAL MEDIA BUYING FEPS Business Incubator

TOT ENTREPRENEURSHIP British Council

MODERN MANAGEMENT SYSTEMS FOR MANAGERS Next Company

# **CURRICULUM VITAE**

**CAREER DEVELOPMENT TRACK** Knowledge Training

**ADVANCED PRESENTATION SKILLS** National Management Institute

BUSINESS WRITING Dale Carnegie Training

CREATIVE THINKING National Quality Institute

TRAINING SKILLS Information Technology Institute

COMMUNICATION SKILLS Information Technology Institute

PRESENTATION SKILLS Information Technology Institute

**EFFECTIVE LEADERSHIP** Egyptian Banking Institute

ORIENTATION COURSE Cisco Academy Fundamentals

TOT NETWORK Information Technology Institute

IT TRAINING PROGRAM IBM Egypt - 300 Hrs. H/W & O.S

**DEVELOPMENT OF BASIC SKILLS IN IT Arab Academy for Science & Technology**